### Contact

+639103176307 (Mobile) rolandwebdeveloper@gmail.co m

www.linkedin.com/in/rolandop-09b66a62 (LinkedIn) pph.me/rolando.parado (Other)

### Top Skills

Jest

WooCommerce

Laravel

### **Publications**

Personal Website Portfolio

# Rolando Parado

Angular Developer at Stampede Design Philippines

## Summary

I am a License Professional Teacher and Web Developer with 10years+ of experience with skillsets in Angular, Angular Material, NgRx, Ionic, Nx.dev, Jest Unit test, RxJS, REST API Consumption, PHP Laravel, WordPress development, and GIT.

## Experience

Stampede

Angular Developer

April 2017 - Present (6 years 4 months)

Malaysia

Angular + REST API Consumption

NGRX State Management

**Typescript** 

**RxJS** 

**Angular Material** 

Jest Unit testing

Aktus Global Management/ Sison Corillo Parone & Co.

Senior Associate

April 2016 - April 2017 (1 year 1 month)

Palo, Leyte

Ecommerce developer using Woocommerce

Team leader

Spiral Web Solutions

Software Developer

March 2015 - March 2017 (2 years 1 month)

United Kingdom

- -PSD to HTML, CSS, Javascript Developer
- -PHP Back-end Developer
- -Responsive Design using Bootstrap
- -WordPress

Accenture
Software Engineering Analyst
April 2015 - February 2016 (11 months)
Region VII - Central Visayas, Philippines

UI Developer, HTML5, Sencha Touch

Odusee Pty Ltd Web Developer April 2013 - March 2015 (2 years) Cebu, City

- -WordPress Developer
- -Woo-commerce integration to WordPress
- -Responsive Design using Bootstrap

RSportz, Inc Software Developer January 2014 - February 2015 (1 year 2 months) California, United States

WordPress Developer
Responsive Web Design
Rails to WordPress development

Municipality of Sta. Fe, Leyte
Web Developer(PHP,MYSQL,xHTML,CSS)(OJT)
April 2011 - June 2011 (3 months)

Web Development and Maintainance of the Current website

SmartMatic - TIM Company
Precinct Count Optical Scanner Technician
May 2010 - May 2010 (1 month)
PCOS Machine Technician

## Education

Eastern Visayas State University

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology · (June 2008 - March 2012)